Guide to the Ingram Olkin papers SC1221
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers
  - Estimating a Constant of Proportionality for Exchangeable Random Variables notes, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Mult Talk NBS, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Schwartz paper - Dayton, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Intruders with pos e., undated (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Psychology Exercises, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Psychology Notes, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Statistics Course-Taking Options for SUSE students, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Problems on Markov Chains, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - An Introduction to Ranking and Selection, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Non-Normal Bivariate Distributions with Normal Marginals, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Notes Matrix Theory Conference, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Estimation for a Regression Model with Covariable, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - A covariance Model, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Reversing Probability and Moment Inequalities, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Applied Statistics and Biometrics, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Status of Reviews, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Unb est in autoregression, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Univ Chi Colloq -- mult anal, 1956 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Gleser, Leon J., 1974-1990 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Language & Math Notation, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Golub, Gene, 1976-1985 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Shanti S. Gupta, 1980-1987 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Goslin, David A., 1986-1987 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Guttman, Irwin, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Bibliographies, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Bibliography - multivariate analysis, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Bibliography - "characterization of distributions", undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Bibliography on bivariate destributions, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Bibliography on outliers, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - AMS, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Affirmative Action, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - ASA Committee on Publications, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - American Mathematical Society Fellowship Panel, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - IMS Committee on Fellows, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Preliminary Report - Chebyshev Bounds for Risks and Error Probabilities in some Classification Problems, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - DERMAN - Master Copy of Rewrite Chapters 6, 7, 8, 9, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Forsythe - vs. Mad-Olkin, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - CIRCLE, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Norms and Inequalities for Condition Numbers, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Tchebycheff & Kolmogorov Inequalities, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Analysis of Covariance, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Proposal for Research Project in Multi-Dimensional Statistical Analysis, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Matrix Theory Notes, undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Guttman, Kim, & Olkin "Statistical Inference for Constants of Proportionality", 1983 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Estimating a Constant of Proportionality for Exchangeable Random Variables, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - The Covariance Matrix of the Maximum Likelihood Estimate of the Mean Vector of a Normal Monotone Sample, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Classification of an Observation into Linear Manifolds, Their Closed Subsets and Closed Convex Subsets, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Univariate Scaling Theory for Linear Models, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Multivariate Scaling Theory for Linear Models, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Annals of Statistics, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Amer. Math Monthly MS 81-049 Directional Derivative, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Other Journals (Misc.), 1983 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Psychological Bulletin Comparing Correlations, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Bhargava Problem, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Hoeffding -- Non-Parametric Autumn Stanford, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Seq. Analysis -- Bibliography, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Stein - Estimation, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Halmos - Savage, undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Gani, Joseph, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Gibbons, Olkin, Sobel Corrections, undated (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - G - O - S Reviews, etc., 1979 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Ghurye, S. G., 1976 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Gifford, Bernard, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Testing for Exponential and Marshall-Olkin Distributions, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Probablity Inequalities for n-Dimensional Rectangles via Multivariate Majorization, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Marshall & Shaked "Multivariate New Better than Used Distributions: A Survey", 1985 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Lieberman, Olkin, Riddle "A Sampling Procedure and Public Policy", 1982 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Group Structure, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Multivariate F Distribution, undated (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Notes and Ineq on Designs, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Bellman Corr, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Mill's Ratio, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Bochner Seminar, undated (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Inequalitypf Szego & Bellman, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Gamma Fcn Inequality -- Gurland, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - STAT 384 Notes, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Olkin/Mudholkar, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Press, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Taussky-Todd & Olkin, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Olkin - Taussky-Todd Notes, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Olkin - Shrikhands, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Olkin Reports - Michigan, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Olkin Reports - Michigan, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - On Distribution Problems in Multivariate Analysis, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Fellows (IO), 2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - MISC. Efron, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - 211-2, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Olkin - Class File, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Olkin - Examinations, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - "Statistical and Theoretical Considerations in Meta-Analysis", 1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Written Examination for Ph.D. in Multivariate Analysis, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Paper on distribution problems & multivariate analysis, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Testing Treatment by Allen, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Lieberman Obits, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - "Meta-Analysis of Observational Studies in Epidemiology", 2000 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Einbinder Corr, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Educ - Mult Class, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Positivity -- Karlin, 1958-1959 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Ohio State External Review, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Olkin Dissertation Advisees, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - STAT 324, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Multivariate, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - STAT 324, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Mathematical Studies of Education Processes notes, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - 250C, 2005 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Dorothy Gilford - ONR, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - July-August Correspondence, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - November-December Correspondence, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Aborn, Murray, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Stat 206 Winter, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - 250A Winter, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - NSF Proposal - Decision Theory, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - 206 Evaluations Winter, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - 250 Summer, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Olkin - Teaching, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Olkin - Seminar Talk Markov Chains, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Olkin - Sabbatic Talks, England, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Stat 314 Classwork Winter, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - IMS - Instrumentation Workshop, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Purdue, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Scaling of Matrices, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Notes on Slepian, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Report, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Annual Faculty Report, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Condition No. III - Mrshall-Olkin, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Math Reviews, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - PHS Grant Application, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Misc papers to be filed, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Olkin Courses, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Course Evaluations, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Henry F. Kaiser, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Academic Press, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Stat 324, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Stat 324, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Admin, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Awards, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1952-1981 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Notes, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Professional, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Publications, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Research Proposals, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Talks, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Teaching, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH_2017_266
  - Papers
    - Research proposals, 1989-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Meta-Analysis, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Good enough (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Good enough, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Good enough (2) Mx Th, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Hinkley- Olkin (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Olkin/Hinkley - On separating treatment and maturation effects (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Characterization of Distributions (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Contamination (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Goldberger - Olkin, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Kastenbaum, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Amer. Acad. Of Forensic Sci, Chi Math Stat in Criminalistics, 1956 Feb (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Criminalistics, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Glasgow AFB, 1965 Oct (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Olkin, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Criminalistics (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Mult Anova, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Hotelling, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Tails of a Distribution (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Generalized inverse, 1972 Dec (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Categorical data (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - misc, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Statistics Operations (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1990 Oct (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Abstracts and Outlines, 1982-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Math notes (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Math lecture notes, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Misc. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Proposal to National Science Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Jose Diaz - Olkin IO papers, MaThai, correspondence, 1998-2005 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Diaz - Garcia papers, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Nanda, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Nanda - Olkin, 1962-1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Nanda and Olkin papers (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - math model, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Jose Diaz - Garcia Functions of Singular Random Matrices, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Diaz - Garcia / Olkin, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Pratt - Olkin Reliab UNB ESJ, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Ranking Selecting pops. Talk - ASA, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Mult. At Chapel Hill, 1948-1963 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Chapel Hill 25 years (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Mult. Chapel Hill (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Chapel Hill, 1951-1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Bartlett, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Fedorov (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - lecture notes, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Testing for equality of 2 correlation coefficients (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Discriminant notes, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Olkin Measures of Heterogeneity, Diversity, and Inequality (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Graphs, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Imperial College Talk on Distributions, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Mx. Conf Transparency, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Gibbons - Olkin - Sobel, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Gibbons, Olkin, Sobel determination of the numbers (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Scoring of Tests, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - From Michael G. Vesselago MD, PS dependency (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Lecture to Leah's 7th grade class on probability (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Lectures at Nees, First Class, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Banff Mx Theory Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Intro lab Irwin Gur., 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Committee on National Statistics folder, 1910-1949 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Inequalities: Theory of Majorization and Applications (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Bayesion Talk (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - from Bernolli Gentration Biv. Dist. (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - MO papers proposals, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Non-normal dsn, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Transparencies (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Educ. Evaluations (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Pajaro Dunes, 1980 Oct (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Matrix theory talk (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Kayseri Talk, 2008 Jun (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Life Distributions and Meta-Analysis, 2007 Jul (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Regression, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Criminalistics, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Mult non-normal xerox (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Matrix Ineq. (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Elaine Allen JSM continuing education course presenter package (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1996 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - non-normal distribution (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Frederickson Problem (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Characterizations of Distributions, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - notes (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - History, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Misconceptions, 2007 Nov (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Talk on Inequality Transparency (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Transparency, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Talk, notes, 2000-2006 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Notes, Publications, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - unlabeled, 1968 Jun (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1968 May (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - unlabeled, 1968 Feb (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - R.A. Fisher - original committee, cops, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - IMS, 1979-1983 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - IMS - Executive Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - IMS presidency, 1983 Aug (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Russian Translation, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Russian Translation Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - RUTrap, 1960 summer (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - RUTRAP, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - S R RUTRAP, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Russian Translations, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Russian Translations, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Statistician comments, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - NSF Women, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Professor Ingram Olkin (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Institute of Mathematical statistics, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Institute of Mathematical statistics, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Proportions #2, 2015 Feb (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Indiv. Patient Data (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Download papers, 2001-2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Notes, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Publications, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - ASA Correspondence, 1983-1989 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - IMS Nominating Committee, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Subcommittee of IMS Committee on Math Tables -- (6) Polyvariate normal, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - IMS Presidency, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - ASA Publications, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - China Multivariate Conference, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Women Fellows (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Publications (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Models for lifetime data (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Pomona (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Notes, 1956-1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Matrix Theory, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - The Interplay Between Probability and Matrix Inequalities, 2007 Sep (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Meta-Analysis: Statistical Methods and Issues, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Viana transp. For talk, other papers, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Paris talk copy of MMO papers (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - JSM Continuing Education Program CE_16C: Meta-Analysis Combining the Results of Multiple Studies, 2011 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Meta-Analysis: Statistical Methods and Issues for Combining the Results of Independent Studies, 2010 Aug (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Multivariate Meta-Analysis: Contributions of Ingram Olkin, 2004 Aug (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Thorny Issues in Collaborative Research, 2014 May (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Moment Inequalities… Ingram Olkin, 2008 Jun (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Measures of Heterogeneity, Diversity and Inequality, 2010 May 21 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - unlabeled, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Preliminary Proposals for a Comprehensive Federal…, 1990 Jul 31 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Apportionment of Seats in Proportional Representation Systems, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Ingram Olkin papers, 1999-2002 Jul 26 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Lancet Discussion - Olkin (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Editors materials David Moler (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Asilomar (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - misc., 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Fifteenth Annual Conference for International Data Management, Epidemiology, and Statistics, and Statistical Programming (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Meta-Analysis: Combining the Results of Multiple Studies, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Belgrade, Hamburg, inequalities/Matrix (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Poland Talk, prob. Ineq. /Mx (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Medical Editors, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - outline, powerpoint, 2000 Aug 16 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Meta-Analysis: Cumulating Evidence from Independent sources, 2014 May 8 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Interpretation of Medical Evidence, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Kayski Talk, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Approximate Confidence Regions for Constraint Parameters (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Goldhaber, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Invitations to speak, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - AERA wojh, 1975 Mar - Apr (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - NSF Women, 1975 Oct (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Unb est - Transparencies (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Olkin - Sobel Asmiss., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Olkin - Selliah, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Admissibility - Olkin and Sobel (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - unlabeled (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Israeli talk Tel. Aviv. (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Misc. (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Worksheets SMDM, 2001 Oct (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - CDC lecture on meta-analysis, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Transparencies for talk, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Meta standards (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Statistics Ingram Olkin (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Robustness - Cov. Matrices (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Styan, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Steffens, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Katz, Lec., 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Rogosa, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Olkin, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Rogosa, 1980-1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Leo Katz - England, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Representation of Disease Etiologies by Certain Stochastic Models by L. Katz, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - O.R., Systems (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Anderson - Herzog - Bellman - Fan, 1957-1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Katz, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Katz, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Patterned Covariences, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Symmetry - Guttman Radex, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - test for symmetry (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Symmetries, 1973 Mar (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Olkin - symmetries (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Notes (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Guttman slides (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Rogosa, David R., 1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Rogosa, David R. (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Technical memorandum Evaluation of Performance Reliability using Regression Models, 1964 Apr (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - History of Multivariate, 1875 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Heterogeneity Quality (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Key Features of Randomized Trials (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Combining Regressions (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Mult. Bose (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Meta-Analysis of Randomized Controlled Trials, 1999 Mar 22-24 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Meta-Analysis Course, 2000 Dec (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Probabilistic Models for Lifetime Data, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - hedges - Olkin unbiased est of Proportions, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Meta- Analysis Course, 1991 Oct 14-15 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Mult. Problems (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Appendix (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1980-2011 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Meta-Analysis, 1988 - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Meta-Analysis: A Quantitative Approach to Research Integration in the Medical and Health Sciences, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1987-2005 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Handwritten notes, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Transparencies (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Query on Meta-correlations, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Handwritten notes (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1974-2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Lecture notes, transparencies, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Misc., 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Handwritten math notes, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Biographical description (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Drafts, publications, 1973-2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Multiv. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Educ. Course notes Human Biology 20, 1979 Jan (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Marshall- Olkins 1) Condition Nos. 2) Mult Exp. (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Ingram, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1970 Oct (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - N-O, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - C, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - F, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Quantitative Synthesis of Research, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Statistical Application Research Union of Japanese Scientists Engineers (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - SRSM 2nd Annual Conference, 2007 Jul 9-11 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - 7th International Workshop on Matrices and Statistics, 1998 Dec 11-14 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Multivariate A-BA, 1957-1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Awards (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - On Distribution Problems in Multivariate Analysis (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Founders Award, 1991-1998 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - pictures (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Photographs (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - TIAA (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Stat Tables (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Lieberman 28th International Conference, 2013 May (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Sign Test (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - media, 1949-2010 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Stat Tables (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Cottle - Matrix Theory (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cohen - Matrix Theory, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Lieberman - Olkin, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Determinant Inequality (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Pukelsheim/Olkin, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Marshall-Olkin Screening and Classification (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - JRCS paper, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Irelim material for JRSS paper - Marshall Olkin, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Screening Classification - Manuscripts - Marshall - Olkin (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - publications, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Quad farms (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Forsythe/Olkin, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Henry Kaiser, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Probability Inequalities, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Est Tails (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - N. Pubs, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Minimax (simpler) attempts (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Corresp. About incorrect pdfs, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Kiefer, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Cholesky Decomp., 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - n Estimators (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Handouts - operations res. Course (Box 7, Folder 22)